export const cv = { 
    portfolio: [
        {front: "portfolio-cover", back: "portfolio_devices_first", links: []}, 
        {front: "portfolio_devices_second", back: "portfolio_burger_first", links: [{text: "Visit 01", link: "https://zaxel.github.io/react_simple_shop"}]}, 
        {front: "portfolio_burger_second", back: "portfolio_resume_first", links: [{text: "Visit 02", link: "https://zaxel.github.io/react_burger_shop"}]},
        {front: "portfolio_resume_second", back: "portfolio_mixed_first", links: [{text: "Visit 03", link: "https://zaxel.github.io/3d_resume"}]}, 
        {front: "portfolio_mixed_second", back: "portfolio_sorter_first", links: [{text: "Visit 04", link: "https://zaxel.github.io/mixed_features_react_app"}]}, 
        {front: "portfolio_sorter_second", back: "portfolio_maze_first", links: [{text: "Visit 05", link: "https://zaxel.github.io/mail_sorter"}]},
        {front: "portfolio_maze_second", back: "portfolio_tetris_first", links: [{text: "Visit 06", link: "https://zaxel.github.io/maze-builder/"}]},
        {front: "portfolio_tetris_second", back: "portfolio_converter_first", links: [{text: "Visit 07", link: "https://zaxel.github.io/tetris/"}]},
        {front: "portfolio_converter_second", back: "portfolio_weather_first", links: [{text: "Visit 08", link: "https://zaxel.github.io/currency-converter"}]},
        {front: "portfolio_weather_second", back: "portfolio_italian-food_first", links: [{text: "Visit 09", link: "https://zaxel.github.io/weatherApp"}]},
        {front: "portfolio_italian-food_second", back: "portfolio_bigmack_first", links: [{text: "Visit 10", link: "https://zaxel.github.io/italian_food"}]},
        {front: "portfolio_bigmack_second", back: "portfolio_italian-cuisine_first", links: [{text: "Visit 11", link: "https://zaxel.github.io/bigmack/"}]},
        {front: "portfolio_italian-cuisine_second", back: "portfolio_mobiler_first", links: [{text: "Visit 12", link: "https://zaxel.github.io/foody"}]},
        {front: "portfolio_mobiler_second", back: "portfolio_carcharger_first", links: [{text: "Visit 13", link: "https://zaxel.github.io/mobiler.com"}]},
        {front: "portfolio_carcharger_second", back: "portfolio_bikeshop_first", links: [{text: "Visit 14", link: "https://zaxel.github.io/car_charger/dist"}]},
        {front: "portfolio_bikeshop_second", back: "cover", links: [{text: "Visit 15", link: "https://zaxel.github.io/bike-shop"}]}, 
    ], 
    profile: [
        {front: "profile-cover", back: "profile_first"}, 
        {front: "profile_second", back: "cover"}, 
    ], 
    skills: [
        {front: "skills-cover", back: "skills_first"}, 
        {front: "skills_second", back: "cover"}, 
    ], 
    history: [
        {front: "history-cover", back: "history_first"}, 
        {front: "history_second", back: "cover"}, 
    ], 
    contacts: [
        {front: "contacts-cover", back: "contacts_first"}, 
        {front: "contacts_second", back: "cover", links: [
            {text: "Call", link: "tel:380676780478"},
            {text: "Mail", link: "mailto:sae11.z.alex@gmail.com"},
            {text: "GitHub", link: "https://github.com/zaxel"},
        ]}, 
    ], 
    hobbies: [
        {front: "hobbies-cover", back: "hobbies_cycling_first"}, 
        {front: "hobbies_cycling_second", back: "hobbies_prehistoric_first"}, 
        {front: "hobbies_prehistoric_second", back: "hobbies_cosmos_first"}, 
        {front: "hobbies_cosmos_second", back: "cover"}, 
    ], 
    credits: [
        {front: "credits-cover", back: "credits_1_first"}, 
        {front: "credits_1_second", back: "credits_2_first", links: [{text: "Visit 01", link: "https://sketchfab.com/3d-models/af05-basic-modeling-dao-pt-6eab61b7a8e3405a9259eebd65cc7ffd"}, {text: "Visit 02", link: "https://sketchfab.com/3d-models/medieval-blacksmith-2e4f2725963644c685419dea1e4430df"}]}, 
        {front: "credits_2_second", back: "credits_3_first", links: [{text: "Visit 03", link: "https://sketchfab.com/3d-models/the-wandering-smith-b64167041c9543f1bfb58a871da5ce1c"}, {text: "Visit 04", link: "https://sketchfab.com/3d-models/tavern-medieval-house-eda03fe47db1450a93a4e2102e4caf65"}]}, 
        {front: "credits_3_second", back: "credits_4_first", links: [{text: "Visit 05", link: "https://sketchfab.com/3d-models/mill-wind-d53ed9dc8f624db9be4c7f3ec22a8e8b"}, {text: "Visit 06", link: "https://sketchfab.com/3d-models/fishermans-house-7df29905b3704e61874d5906db9f0a75"}]}, 
        {front: "credits_4_second", back: "credits_5_first", links: [{text: "Visit 07", link: "https://sketchfab.com/3d-models/dreamy-bridge-50c3313a16c740a4b02d0ff2e2441889"}, {text: "Visit 08", link: "https://sketchfab.com/3d-models/old-bridge-6441316f4195400f80d5bdcbfe835d30"}]}, 
        {front: "credits_5_second", back: "credits_6_first", links: [{text: "Visit 09", link: "https://sketchfab.com/3d-models/bridge-9328bbfc04a84202a6a97bd59408473a"}, {text: "Visit 10", link: "https://sketchfab.com/3d-models/medieval-notice-board-6b81d6df32724396bd56e79f6774b25f"}]}, 
        {front: "credits_6_second", back: "cover", links: [{text: "Visit 11", link: "https://sketchfab.com/3d-models/the-medieval-book-stand-3e736d23b3f44f0d859b40a4fc13af0d"}, {text: "Visit 12", link: "https://sketchfab.com/3d-models/stylized-wood-signs-d529ec8478304d45a5048e15cf9cc9db"}]}, 
    ], 
};

